A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Declination Lists, SG 18.1 FA1861
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Declination Lists, SG 18.1
1930-1993
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA1861
11.17 Cubic Feet 25 containers including: 22 letter document boxes, 2 record storage boxes and 1 half-letter document box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Records more than 20 years old are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
As received. Primarily chronological. Declination Lists are arranged by year, and alphabetical. Reports are generally by year and program.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains declination lists and associated reports. Each annual report of declinations includes summaries by program and/or division. As applicable within a given year, the programs documented include but are not limited to: Ariculture; Agricultural Sciences; Arts; Biological and Medical Research; Central Administration; Humanities; Humanities and Social Sciences; Hungarian Emergency Aid Program; International Health; Medical Education and Public Health; Medicine and Public Health; and Villa Serbelloni (Bellagio, Italy).
- International - Declinations - Declination Lists, 1930-1993; 100F; 11.17 Cubic Feet 25 containers including: 22 letter document boxes, 2 record storage boxes and 1 half-letter document box.
  - New York Office, Paris Office, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - New York Office, Paris Office, China Office, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - New York Office, 1934-1939 September (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
  - New York Office, 1939 October-1948 (Box 2, Folder 7-12)
  - New York Office, 1949-1952 (Box 3, Folder 13-18)
  - New York Office, 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 19-24)
  - New York Office, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 25-29)
  - New York Office, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 30-34)
  - New York Office, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 35-40)
  - New York Office, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 41-46)
  - New York Office, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 47-50)
  - New York Office, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 51-57)
  - New York Office, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 102-103, Box 22, Folder 104)
  - New York Office, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 105-107)
  - China Office, 1932-1942 (Box 22, Folder 108)
  - Delhi Office, 1942-1943 (Box 22, Folder 109)
  - Far Eastern Office, 1944-1957 (Box 22, Folder 110)
  - India Office, 1958-1969 (Box 22, Folder 111)
  - London Office, 1948-1954, 1956-1963 (Box 23, Folder 112)
  - Madras Office, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 113)
  - Paris Office, 1934-1940, 1947-1958 (Box 23, Folder 114)
  - Rio de Janeiro Office, 1957-1962 (Box 23, Folder 115)
  - Declination Lists - Index, 1930s-1961 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Declination Lists - Index, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 59-60)
  - Declination Lists - Index, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Declination Lists, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 62-64)
  - Declination Lists, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 65, Box 13, Folder 66-67)
  - Declination Lists, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 68-69)
  - Declination Lists, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 70, Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Declination Lists, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 72-74)
  - Declination Lists, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 75-78)
  - Declination Lists, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 79, Box 16, Folder 80-81)
  - Declination Lists, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 82-84, Box 17, Folder 85-86)
  - Declination Lists, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 87-89)
  - Declination Lists, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 90-92)
  - Declination Lists, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - Declination Lists, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Declination Lists, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Declination Lists, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 96, Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Declination Lists, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Declination Lists, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 99, Box 21, Folder 100-101)
  - Declinations - Alphabetical Index, 1971-1975 (Box 24)
  - Declinations - Alphabetical Index, 1976; 1979; 1986 (Box 25)